BHUMI MANDALIA

ABOUT ME

I am a GRAPHIC DESIGNER. Currently I am working in DVIO Digital, Pune. I have 3.6 years of experience in Web Designing, Graphic Design, UI Design, banner design, Print Ads, Digital Marketing. I'm looking for suitable opening in designing where I can explore my skill.

EDUCATION

Completed High School in 2010 from Manikrupa highschool, Ahmedabad.
Completed B.E.(Computer Engineering) in 2014 from GEC, Gandhinagar.

EXPERIENCE

7i Webtech (Feb, 2016 - Dec, 2016)

I have worked on Website Design, Image Editing, Banner.

Rubiksweb Technology (Jan, 2017 - July, 2017)
I have worked on Website design, App design, Logo,
Flyer, Banner, Image editing.

Hikebranding (Aug, 2017 - March 2019)
I have worked on Website design, Logo, Flyer, Banner,
Image editing, Brouchers.

Dvio Digital pvt.lmt.(March 2019 - Till now)
I have worked on Digital Marketing, Flyer, Emailers,
Banner, Posters, Brouchers, Print Ads.

SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Corel Draw

DESIGNER ABILITIES

Web design, Graphic design, Digital Marketing, App design, User interface, Print ads, Posters Branding, Brochure, Infographic, Emailers.

CONTACT

ADDRESS

B2/12, Raagdari apartment, DP road, Aundh, Pune.

EMAIL ADDRESS

bhumi009g5@gmail.com

MOBILE NO.

7990239592